theworks.co.uk 2012-10-30

# Privacy Policy - The Works

##  The Works - Our Privacy Statement 

At The Works we are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding ways in which your personal data is used. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to our processing, please contact us on: 0121 313 6000 or email Customer Services [enquiries@theworks.co.uk](mailto:enquiries@theworks.co.uk)

Information collected

The Works Retail Ltd is the sole owner of information collected. 

The system collects the details provided by you on registration, together with information we learn about you from your use of our service and your visits to our web site and other sites accessible from there. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake, including details of payment cards used. 

We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions, competitions or surveys offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback or completing profile forms. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site use, which enables us to improve the service we provide. 

Use of your information and your preferences

We will use your information to provide and personalise our services. We will also use your contact details to communicate with you. We may use your information to send you offers and news about us and our products. We  do not share personal information with third parties, except for the purposes of credit/debit card authorisation and delivery. We may contact you by post, email, telephone or fax for these purposes. 

As soon as you become a registered site user, you will be provided with the option to receive commercial communications from us, please tick the box if you would like to receive commercial communications. 

We like to hear your views to help us improve our service. From time-to-time we may contact you by post, email, telephone and fax to ask your opinions. Again, if you do not want to be contacted for this purpose, please make your choice where indicated. 

Please note, there may be instances where it may be necessary for us to communicate with you, in any event, for administrative or operational reasons relating to our service. 

Disclosures of your information

Your information may be passed to and used by other companies within the group. We will  never pass your personal data to anyone else, except for any successor's in title to our business and suppliers that process data on our behalf. We may also use and disclose information in aggregate 

(so that no individual customers are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes. 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, wherein we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a Court Order or legal process served on our web site. 

Other web sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites, which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you, which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. 

Cookies

'Cookies' are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. You can find out more about the way cookies work on cookiecentral.com . We use the cookies for a number of purposes, for instance to enable us to simplify the logging-on process for registered users, to help ensure the security and authenticity of registered users, to provide the mechanisms for online shopping and to enable traffic monitoring. 

Non-registered visitors of the site are sent anonymous cookies to keep track of their browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile. In addition, any visitor who has clicked on our advertisement on another site that links to us will be sent a semi-persistent (e.g. one week's lifetime) anonymous cookie that will allow us to analyse advertising effectiveness and manage our relationship with affiliate sites, if any. 

Whilst you do not need to allow your browser to accept cookies in order to browse much of our web site or to access many of our services, you must have cookies enabled if you wish to shop online at any of our stores or access any areas reserved for registered users. 

Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookie function. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. As described above, this will restrict some of our services you can use. 

Correcting/Updating/Deleting Personal Information

If a user's personally-identified information changes (such as postcode, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, then please contact us by email [websales@theworks.gb.com](mailto:cs@theworks.gb.com) , post or telephone. 

###   

###  Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post these changes on our homepage. If there are changes to the way personal information is being used which differs from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users who have opted in by email. 

Contact details:- 

THE WORKS RETAIL LTD   
Midpoint Park  
Sutton Coldfield  
West Midlands  
England  
B76 1RN

Tel:  0121 313 6000
